

# **GEERTHIKA LAKSHMANAN**

## **UI/UX** Designer

Tamilnadu 630301, India argeerthi14@gmail.com (+91)9095232109

LinkedIn | Behance

Portfolio Link:

www.geerthika.com

#### **EDUCATION**

2022

Designboat UI/UX School, (Certified) Bangalore, India

2015-2020

B.Arch, Department of Architecture & Design, Anna University, Chennai, India

#### **SKILLS**

Software	Design
Figma	UX Research
Sketch	Design System
Adobe XD	UI Design
Invision	Qualitative Analysis
Framer	Quantitative Analysis
Google Analytics	Tokens & Assets
Adobe Photoshop	Web/Mobile Design
Adobe Illustrator	Wireframing
Adobe Indesign	Prototype & Test

## **Programming**

HTML
CSS
Bootstrap
JavaScript

#### **LANGUAGES**

English - Fluent
Tamil - Native
Hindi - Intermediate
(curious to learn more)

#### **ABOUT**

A blend of UI/UX and Architecture. 3 years of experience in design field with Positive attitude, Adaptability and Reliablity. My expertise has been in E-commerce, WEB 3.0 Blockchain Industry, HealthCare, Fintech products - with IOS, Android & Website Design. Knowledge of HTML5 and CSS3 with respect to design. I'm open to relocation for the right opportunity.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### UX UI Designer (Oct 2022 - Present)

GeekyAnts, Bangalore - Product company, Experience in UX Design Building Design system. Collaborated with product managers, designers, developers and marketing team to iterate and report the findings of the Responsible design deliverables of Geeklego.io using design sprint process. Designer of framework MVP with successful product launch.

#### User Experience Designer (June 2022 - August 2022)

Redd Experience Design (Company Merged) - B2C Worked on the crypto blockchain WEB 3.0 Design System - Mobile, I contributed to the task of redesigning the marketing collaterals for the brand Persistence One with digital wallet Interface Design including the pitch deck, BNB Deck, and Design documentation.

## UI UX Designer (June 2021 - May 2022)

Freelance Designer B2B - Design thinking process, (designing LoFi / HiFi mockups) Persona, Journey maps, Building and maintaining a design system, User flow, competitive research, HCI, wireframe and clickable prototype. Challenging collaboration with startups in 2D and 3D contents, Storyboard and Colour psychology.

#### Junior Designer (Jan 2020 - Oct 2021)

HCP Design Planning & Management pvt.ltd, Ahmedabad - Worked on the project of 'Central Vista Redevelopment of India, Delhi'.

Communication and Visual Design - Indian government presentation deliverables. Mock-ups, design guidelines and Typography.

## Internship (June 2018 - March 2019)

SR+A Architects, Mumbai - Architecture Internship